<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Asus ROG Phone 2 RGB</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Animations</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Colour Wheel</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_animations">AnimationsActivity</string>
    <string name="about_text">Hello There Ladies and Gentlemen.\n
        This app allows you to control the logo and second rgb on custom roms.\n\n

        You need to be rooted to use this since it writes to system files.\n\n

        To use it press the power button on the bottom right of the screen.\n
        When it turns green we are good to go and you can head over the animations tab.\n\n

        The Colour wheel allows you to change the colour provided the animations aren\'t rainbow.\n
        Colour wheel will work for the following animations.\n
        solid one colour\n
        breathing one colour\n
        blink\n
        some kind of thunder\n
        quick two flashes\n
        and sort of the last one too\n\n

        Notification support added and you can mess around with the settings after clicking on \"notification settings\"\n
        To use the notifications\n
        1. Press on the notification settings to see the options.\n
        2. Press on React to Notifications to start the service.\n
        3. Press on the \"Click to enable app to read notifications in settings\" button and allow Asus Rog Phone 2 RGB to read notifications\n
        4. Select which animation you want to run when there is a notification\n
        5. Press on \"Select which apps trigger notifications\" and tick on all the apps you want the app to use leds when a notification come in.\n\n

        You can also enable the use of the second led that\'s normally meant to be used with a custom case.\n
        The \"enable second led\" switch above \"Notification settings\" switch enables the second led for any animations selected above. This doesn\'t have any impact on using the second led for notifications.\n\n

        For notifications you now have the following options relating to the second led.\n
        \"use second led for notifications also\" This lights up the second led and the logo led when a notification comes in.\n
        \"Use Only the second led for notifications\" This lights up only the second led.\n
        If you have both 1 and 2 disabled then only the logo led with light up.\n\n

        Notifications now can be snoozed. You can set up a time period where the notification service does not run. This is especially useful for rog 3 users as rog 3 needs a wakelock for notifications to work\n\n

        If you like what I do you can check out my github, youtube and telegram channel by clicking the icons at the top.\n\n

        If you would like to donate :) click on the paypal or patreon icons up above\n\n

        Thanks and Bye Bye
    </string>

    <!--
    This string is used for square devices and overridden by hello_world in
    values-round/strings.xml for round devices.
    -->
    <string name="hello_world">Hello Square World!</string>

    <string-array name="notification_animations">
        <item>solid one colour</item>
        <item>breathing one colour</item>
        <item>blink</item>
        <item>rainbow</item>
        <item>another rainbow?</item>
        <item>rainbow breathe</item>
        <item>somekind of thunder</item>
        <item>thunder rainbow</item>
        <item>quick two flashes</item>
        <item>quick two flashes rainbow</item>
        <item>breathe rainbow</item>
        <item>some strange breathe rainbow</item>
        <item>slow glitchy rainbow</item>
        <item>Developers custom anim</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_app_selector">AppSelector</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
</resources>